exeloncorp.com 2014-05-27

# Exelon Corporation: Privacy Policy

You should exercise discretion in what information you send to us by email.  We cannot guarantee that email sent over the internet is secure and will not be intercepted by others before it reaches us.   We are not responsible for the security of information contained in emails sent over the internet.  We do not use technology that automatically collects personally identifiable information from you through this web site such as name, address, telephone number, or email address. 

We do not disclose or sell any personal information about you to third parties without your prior approval, except as required by law, requested by regulatory agencies and governmental authorities, arises from the sale of all or a portion of any of its businesses, or is used for legitimate business purposes. Information collected on this web site may be used to better provide you with Exelon's services. From time to time, we may change our privacy policy, and will make reasonable efforts to publish such changes. Furthermore, we adhere to strict security procedures in an effort to more fully protect your information. 

## Collecting and using personal information 

When you submit personal information to us, you are agreeing to permit us and our subsidiaries and affiliates to access, store, and use the information wherever in the world we and our subsidiaries and affiliates do business, both inside and outside the United States.  However, BGE, ComEd and PECO will share customer information with their affiliates only to the extent permitted by applicable law and regulation.  In particular, we may use your personal information for various business purposes, such as statistical analyses, generating surveys, doing market research, improving its services, and notifying you about services and changes that may affect you, among other business purposes. 

## Who should use this web site

Exelon's web site is intended to provide general information about Exelon and its services.  Exelon's web site is intended for adults and not children under 18.  Exelon will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age, nor allow children under the age of 13 to use certain features of our website without the consent of a child's parent or guardian. Exelon will not knowingly disclose personal information collected from children.

**External Links  
**In some cases, our web site links to other sites that collect personal information by and for other parties.  In these cases, the personal information you provide on those sites is governed by the privacy policy of that site.  We do not assume responsibility for the actions of other parties.  However, we will use reasonable efforts to maintain secure connections with you and limit access to databases containing your personal information to authorized parties, including our own employees, whose access to your information is on a need to know basis.

## "Cookie" use 

"Cookies" are small text files that are stored on your computer's hard drive by a web site through your browser. "Cookies" enable a website such as ours to keep track of your activities on that website, and to improve your use of the site, such as by keeping track of your preferences. "Cookies" do not include any personal information. Additionally, you can change your browser settings on your personal computer so that "cookies" are not stored on your hard drive. 

## Disclosure to government 

We reserve the right to monitor and disclose, without your consent, any communications or personal information, whenever requested to do so by courts, government agencies or by law enforcement authorities. 

We will use reasonable efforts to address concerns you may have about your personal information. You may contact us by using the "Contact Us" area of the site. 

**Last updated: March 12, 2012**
